Kenan McKenzie

mckenzie.kenan@yahoo.com mckenzie.kenan@yahoo.com, North Carolina, 28027 mckenzie.kenan@yahoo.com 7047944324

Programmer

I am just graduating from the UNC-Charlotte Full-Stack Programming Boot Camp where I learned many javascript frameworks including React, Handlebars, Express, Node, Mongoose and more. It has been one of the more challenging and rewarding experiences of my life and I am excited to see where I can take my career from here

Professional Experience

Customer Advocate

Shipping Supervisor

Image First | December 2020 - Present

age First | December 2020 - Present

Ashley Furniture | March 2016 - December 2020

Deliver linen to hospitals mainly in Charlotte. Build relationships based on trust and communication to keep up with providers needs to ensure all of their patients have a quality experience.

Worked my way up from loading trucks to managing 30+ employees to meet hourly/daily/weekly inventory goals in a very physically and mentally demanding environment.

Was chosen to lead the inaugural e-commerce department which was formed at the onset of covid.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Communication and Marketing

Appalachian State University at Boone, NC

HS Diploma

East Rowan High School at Salisbury, NC | 2008

Key Skills

- Hard worker
- Fast learner
- Good coworker and employee